Angel Gabriel Salvador Castañeda

Software engineer



PHONE 3122001950

LINKS Github, Linkedin

EMAIL 02angelsalvador@gmail.com

Profile

I'm a student in the career Software Engineer of the University of Colima. My main skills are focused on web development but also like to program in C ++. I have some experience working in web development with real clients. Since 2017 I have been in a dependency of the university making projects with them, some with external clients of the university and many internal, in that dependency, I worked with databases, front-end and back-end. Another particular thing about me is that I like to solve problems because I learn from them.

Skills

HTML5 & CSS3

PHP

Mysql

SQL

Ability to Work in a Team

jQuery

Git

Vue js

Employment History

Feb 2017 - Aug 2019

Front-end and Back-end developer

COLIMA, COL.

Dirección de Sistemas - Universidad de Colima

In this university department, I worked with technology like Php, Javascript, SQL, Mysql for database, Css3, Html5, Javascript vanilla and Jquery for Front-end and Git for version control.

Sep 2018 - Sep 2019

Front-end developer

COLIMA, COL.

Coddy (www.coddy.com.mx)

In this company, I had a part-time job and I worked with technology like vanilla js, Vue js, HTML5, CSS3 and Jquery in some projects and Git for version control.

Education

Aug 2016 - Present

University of Colima

COLIMA, COL.

Software engineer

Languages

English

TOEFL Exam Score: 380

Spanish

Native Language